http://www.kennys.ie/privacy-policy

Log in
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Create an account
Remember Me
Close Register
Categories
Art & ArchitectureBiographyBusiness & FinanceChildren's & Young AdultComics & Graphic NovelsComputingCrimeDrama & TheatreFictionFiction (Secondhand)Food & DrinkGAA / Irish SportHealth & Personal DevelopmentHistoryHome & GardenIrish HistoryIrish LiteratureLawLeabhair GhaeilgeLiteratureLiterature (Secondhand)Local HistoryMind, Body & SpiritMusic & EntertainmentNatural HistoryPoetryPoliticsReferenceRomanceScience & TechnologySci-Fi & FantasySportTravelOther Categories
Home » Privacy Policy
We Are Committed To Protecting Your Privacy
We are committed to protecting your privacy in all aspects of our business and we hope you will take the time to read this policy. This policy explains what information we collect from you and how we use that information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will endeavor to post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to. You are kindly requested to check back periodically for any changes to this policy. By using the books.kennys.ie web site and purchasing from us, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Purchase By Children
It is our policy not to sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use the Kennys.ie web sites only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.
The Information We Collect And How We Use It
When you visit the Kennys.ie web sites, we may collect your IP address in order to diagnose problems or issues with our server and to improve the manner in which we sell to you, our customer. Your IP address is not used identify you in any manner but helps us to gather broad demographic information.
The www.kennys.ie web site uses "cookies," which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but enable us to provide a shopping cart and to store your order information between visits. If you've set your browser to reject cookies, you can still use our site, but will not be able to purchase items. We recommend that you leave them turned on
To request more information about an item, you must provide your e-mail address so that we may reply to your question by e-mail. To order from us you must set up an account. Setting up an account requires you to provide your email address and choose a password. We also ask for your name, shipping address, telephone number (your "Order Information"). This information is necessary for us to process your order, to notify you of your order status, and to fulfill orders. We do not provide any personal information such as your e-mail address or billing information to any third party.
Kennys have a formal arrangement with a secure third party site [Realex Payments] where you must enter your credit card number, billing address, and expiration date to secure payment. Realex Payments uses a secure server. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts all information you input. The security of this procedure is such that Kennys are not given access to you credit card information. We are simply instructed by Realex Payments that the credit card has been authorized. Realex Payments are not permitted to use your information for any other purposes than to secure payment for you purchase from us.
Alternatively you may pay through Paypal or Stripe, which are also secure third party sites.
You may from time to time choose not to use our third party secure sites and may send us your credit card details directly. While we cannot be responsible for the manner in which you transmit this information, we can assure you that credit card details will be used to process a payment and then destroyed. Access to this information shall be strictly limited to authorized personnel and shall not be transmitted or divulged to any third party.
We may use your Order Information to occasionally notify you about important changes to this policy, our terms and conditions, changes on our Web site, new features, or special offers that you may find useful. If you would rather not receive this information, you may emailThis email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.(Please make sure to inform us of your wishes for each account or email address you have left with us.)
If you subscribe to the Kennys Mailing List, we will occasionally notify you about important changes to this policy, our terms and conditions, changes on our Web site, new features, and most importantly, information and special offers that relate to your categories of interest. If you wish to modify the categories that are of interest to you or if you would rather not receive any further information, you may emailThis email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. (Please make sure to inform us of your wishes for each account or email address you have left with us.)
You may also choose to provide personal information, such as your name and address, when you enter a contest. We may use this information the same way we use your Order Information.
We protect your information
The Kennys.ie web sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. When you place orders or access your account information, all of the customer data we collect is similarly protected against unauthorized access.
Link to other Web sites
The Kennys.ie web sites may contain links to other sites, operated by third parties, that we think may be of interest to you. Kennys will not share your information with these third parties. These third parties are encouraged by us to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, but we are not responsible for the actions of those parties, the content of their Web sites, or any products or services they may offer.
Contact Us About Our Privacy Policy
We welcome any comments about our privacy policy [positive or negative]. Please send all feedback to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.e
